Guide to the Botany Dept. records, 1877-1893.
Botany Dept. records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Botany Dept. records, 1877-1893.
14-29-2026
Cornell University. Botany Dept.
.3 cubic ft.
Financial records, photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Two small volumes of inventory and financial records, 1877-1890, 1888-1893; and photographs of staff and facilities of the Cornell University Botany Department, now the Section of Plant Biology.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Two small volumes of inventory and financial records, 1877-1890, 1888-1893; and photographs of staff and facilities of the Cornell University Botany Department, now the Section of Plant Biology.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University -- Faculty.; Cornell University. Section of Plant Biology.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Matted Photographs (Box 1)
  - Systematic Botany and Histology Lab, Sage College(1st Floor), c.1890 (Box 1)
  - Library Slope, c.1898 (Box 1)
    Notes Fiske-McGraw Mansion
  - Library Slope, c.1898 (Box 1)
  - Elementary Botany Lab and Lecture Room, c.1898 (Box 1)
  - Elementary Botany Lab and Lecture Room, Sage College, c.1898 (Box 1)
    2 copies of the same photograph
  - Elementary Botany Lab and Lecture Room, Sage College, c.1898 (Box 1)
  - Elementary Botany Club and Lecture Room, Sage College, c.1898 (Box 1)
  - Sage College, Botany Greenhouses, c.1898 (Box 1)
  - Common types of planting on campus, c.1898 (Box 1)
  - B.M. Duggar, c.1900 (Box 1)
  - Entfield Trip on honor of Dr. Paul Magnus, c.1900 (Box 1)
    2 copies of the same photograph. Persons in the photograph listed: B.M. Duggar, G.T> Atkinson, K.M. Wiegand, F.C. Stewart, and C. Magnus
  - Sage Avenue before relocation, c.1900 (Box 1)
  - Renwick (now Stewart) Park, c.1900 (Box 1)
  - Waite School Athletic Field - Now Thurston Ave. and Fall Circle Drive, c.1900 (Box 1)
    Fiske-McGraw mansion left, "Knoll" at right
  - Collecting Isoetes, Cortland Marl Ponds, c.1900 (Box 1)
  - Collecting Isoetes, Cortland Marl Ponds, c.1900 (Box 1)
  - Collecting Isoetes, Cortland Marl Ponds, c.1900 (Box 1)
    B.M. Duggar, K.M. Wiegand
  - Type of planting common on campus, c.1900 (Box 1)
  - Saw Mill at "Chicago", c.1900 (Box 1)
  - Location now Bargholtz Park, c.1900 (Box 1)
    Picture of circus tents
  - Sage College Conservatories, c.1900 (Box 1)
  - Sage Conservatories, c.1900 (Box 1)
  - Greenhouse Staff and S. Side Sage College, c.1900 (Box 1)
    Robert Shore, Jr., Robert Shore Sr., Cornelious Kennelly
  - "Con" himself (Box 1)
    "Janitor and Green h.man (a real character)"
  - Undated and Untitled Matted Photographs, c.1898-1900 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Volumes (Box 1)
  - Inventory, 1877-1896 (Box 1)
    Ledger notebook of finances
  - Cornell University Experiment Station Botanical Department - Copies of bills for goods and purchases, 1888-1893 (Box 1)